myminifactory.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy

**2\. IP ADDRESSES**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

 **3\. COOKIES**

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website and it will recognise your device on future visits. These “cookies" can be divided into 4 types each of which is outlined below:

 **Category 1:** Strictly Necessary Cookies: These cookies are essential in order to enable the site to provide services you have asked for such as remembering your shopping bag items.

 **Category 2:** Performance Cookies: This type collect anonymous information on how people use the site and the data is merged with other users to enable us to improve how the site operates. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.

 **Category 3:** Functionality Cookies: These remember choices you make such as language, search parameters such as size, colour or product line. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate with your selections and make the visits more tailored and pleasant.

 **Category 4:** Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies: These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers.

You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer or mobile device without your explicit consent. Your browser "Privacy" section (under Options or Preferences) will normally provide details on how to manage the cookie settings. Changing cookie settings may disable or reduce the functionality available to you in certain areas of our website.

**4\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the EEA where you may not have the benefit of rights granted under EU Data Protection legislation. If you would like to know more about how we protect your data please contact info@myminifactory.com. It may also be processed by staff working outside the EU who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**5\. USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

(a) To process any quotation request we shall provide your data to such third parties to respond to such quotation request.

(b) To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

(c) To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

(d) To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.

Third parties may also access your data, with your explicit consentement, via our APIs (application programming interfaces). You can revoke access third parties via your account applications management.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these from time to time.

Once you have made an enquiry, we may from time to time contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services we think may be of interest to you.

**6\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

(a) In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

(b) If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**7\. CHILDREN AND OUR SERVICES  
**

You must be 16 years of age to consent to the processing of your personal data in your country. Under 16 years old you must allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf. In doupt, we may contact you to verify your age.

**8\. YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at the contact point below.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

You have the right to request deletion of your personal data. You can do so from the privacy settings in your profile.

**9\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.

You have the right to request your personal data. You can do so from the privacy settings in your profile.

**10\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

**11\. CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to: info@myminifactory.com.
